<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:09:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recustomizing My KDE Plasma</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/customizing-the-kde-plasma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:09:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/customizing-the-kde-plasma/</guid>
      <description>A couple or three days ago, I recustomized the KDE desktop environment. While customizing the desktop environment, I remembered that back in 2021, I found a sci-fi-looking theme that would nicely fit with my KDE setup. I briefly used it in 2021, but I will be using it much longer on my new setups (new meaning two and three years old computers).&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s a little story, I was running Arch Linux on the old desktop that ran an Athlon 64 processor (I cannot remember the exact generation of this CPU, but it was somewhere around 3xxx or 2xxx), 2GB RAM, and Windows XP preinstalled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distro Review and Usage</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/distroreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 11:06:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/distroreview/</guid>
      <description>I have tried various distros on a couple of my computers (three including my Raspberry Pi). Many popular distros have a reputation for being robust for a Linux user. Then, there are less used Linux distros that I think created a new and smart concept. In contrast, some Linux distros did not work on my computers for some reason.&#xA;I am using a Dell Inspiron with a 360°-flippable touchscreen. I attach an external hard drive to the USB port of my laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:46:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/intro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Kerbsite! Let&amp;rsquo;s introduce Jool! Jool is an author of this site. He is a college man in real life. He likes astronomy, computers, languages, and geography. He plays Kerbal Space Program, Endless Sky, and SuperTuxKart. He also uploads videos too, but the rate that he uploads is slowing down. He has some social media sites that are listed in social media links and usernames.&#xA;He is on video social media sites including YouTube, Twitch, Rumble, and Odysee.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
